Can I have another one, please?
Oh, sorry, I'll tape-stitch it.
I'll go get some tea.
Bought it.
Night Tidings
Yes, it was an early ending.
So early...
Okay, now, I have an announcement from Haruna Sakamoto. Here you go!
Yes, Team Shachi Second EP Awaiting Bear is now on sale!
Four of the strongest songs, written by Kenta Matsukuma, are hot!
It's just so emo! Fast and happy!
Please listen to the songs that will make you feel all kinds of emotions. Please listen to them.
And, every Thursday night from 10 p.m. on CBC radio, we are broadcasting "Oshimashi".
The title of this program is "Oshimashi," and it is a wonderful program to spread the word about your guesses,
We are looking forward to hearing your guesses in the messages. Please send us your guesses by message.
In addition, there will be a live performance.
We belong to Team Shachie, to which I also belong. I belong to Team Shachi.
This is an event in which three groups, Iginari Tohoku-san x Shoujo-tai, will perform.
Stapler Localism Vol.3 Make it a sister city! Shokudare Osaka City version will be held in Osaka on September 30.
Osaka, he said.
I'm in Osaka.
Do you want to come?
Oh, but let's come.
Oh, but let's come.Oh, but let's come.
Localism is a group that has a unique sense of unity or atmosphere that is only possible because it is a regional group,
I am looking forward to seeing what kind of atmosphere the three groups will create together with their fans, so let's make Osaka a hot place.
I look forward to seeing what kind of atmosphere the three groups will create together with their fans.
I have one question: What is that strange takoyaki-like thing with a psyllium in the announcement image?
What is it? I also thought it was strange.
I have asked many people what it was, but all they say is that they were there when they noticed it?
I noticed it too, and it suddenly appeared with a cute logo, so I wondered if it was there that day.
What? What? What?
What? Huh? Maybe he's somewhere else that day,
It remains a mystery.
It was a mysterious creature,
Yes, it was.
Please check it out, everyone.
Please keep the information coming.
Thank you very much.
Next, here it is.
On Sunday, October 29, we will be performing at the Stapler Idol Festival Autumn New Song Harvest Festival at Yokohama Arena.
I am looking forward to it.
I'm sure you will be able to meet a lot of junior and senior members backstage.
Do you want to take pictures with anyone or meet this girl?
I want to hold off on Eve Eve and Nako. I want to hold off on Eve Eve and Nako-chan.
Lastly, I, Kakan-kun, would like to give you a cup of tea to cheer you up.
This time, it is a herbal tea bag for sore throats.
Bon appétit.Bon appétit.
Mmm. It's good.
Delicious. I'm glad.
I worked hard too. It was worth it to make the tea.
Oh, it's delicious. I knew it. It's good herbs.
Now that you've relaxed in that way.
And now that you've relaxed in that way... we'll come to the end of Haruna Sakamoto's talk.
Any last words?
I'm going to keep on having fun... and cheering for the inspiring Haruna Sakamoto.
Please continue to support the fun-loving and inspirational Haruna Sakamoto.
I hope you will all continue to support the fun-loving and inspiring Haruna Sakamoto.
That's all for now, this is Haruna Sakamoto.
Bye bye!
This program is presented by
Goripon
Kensuke
Mr. Kuribon
Mr. Tosakamin
Torokko-san
Thank you very much for your kind attention!
I'm going to sleep a lot today.
Good night.